It's why this idea of community standards is really such a farce, because we know that these
are being selectively enforced by a very powerful group of people. And we know that the victims are
going to be the rest of all of us who are trying to fight for freedom, not just against genocide,
but also for liberation from the river to the sea. The problem is imperialism. The problem is
capitalism. Why is the prime minister of the genocidal regime sitting down with social media
influencers, right? We have a very particular example of how Palestinians are directly
racialized and targeted by big tech, which is also facilitating the Zionist physical process of
settler colonization through the digital sphere. People like Jordana Cutler, who worked for Netanyahu
and now serves as a meta executive. The deletion of these accounts is precisely the deletion of
archival evidence of genocide, right? This is a real time attempt to silence people who are trying
to document genocide, to document colonial atrocities, and to galvanize international
support. It's a continuous struggle on these platforms in the same way that it's a continuous
struggle in the Palestine liberation movement more broadly.